Guide to the National Guardian Photographs PHOTOS.213
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- El Salvador Economy, 1984-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Anti-Apartheid, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Anti-Apartheid Demonstrations, 1988-; 1.0 folder (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Anti-Apartheid, 1985-; 2.0 folders (Box 7, Folder 14-15)
- Anti-Apartheid, 1986-; 1.0 folder (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Anti-Apartheid, 1987-; 1.0 folder (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Demonstrations Anti-Nuke, 1988-; 1.0 folder (Box 7, Folder 18)
- AIDS Demonstrations, 1989-; 1.0 folder (Box 7, Folder 19)
- ABC Strike California, 1988-; 1.0 folder (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Demonstrations, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Demonstrations – AIDS, 1987-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Demonstrations – Animal Rights, 1989-; 1.0 folder (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Disarmament Demonstrations, 1982-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Disarmament/Hiro-Nagasaki Day Protests, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 7, Folder 25)
- AIDS Testing, 1987-; 1.0 folder (Box 7, Folder 26)
- AIDS Demonstrations, 1988-; 1.0 folder (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Demonstrations – miscellaneous, International, 1980-1987; 2.0 folders (Box 7, Folder 28-29)
- Anti-Contra Aid, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Demonstrations/Central America, 1985-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Anti-Contra Aid Demonstrations, 1987-; 1.0 folder (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Contra Aid Protests, 1988-; 1.0 folder (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Nica Contra Aid, 1984-1986; 2.0 folders (Box 7, Folder 34-35)
- Students, 1989-; 1.0 folder (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Demonstrations VS Bush, 1989-; 1.0 folder (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Demonstrations Black, 1965-1983; 1.0 folder (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Death Penalty, 1981-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Demonstrations African Support, 1980-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Free Press/Censorship, 1989-; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Demonstrations – Anti-CIA, 1985-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 2)
- CIA Demonstrations, Apr. 27,1987-; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Demonstrations – Anti-Contra Aid, 1986-; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Democratic Presidential Candidates 1984, 1982-1984; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Central America/ Contra Aid, 1988-; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Demonstrations and Protests, 1949-1989; 15.0 folders (Box 8, Folder 1-15)
- Agribusiness, undated; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Farmers Strikes, 1977-; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Livestock, 1968-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Agriculture Equipment (Industry & Labor), 1965-; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Farms Old and New, 1947-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Native Americans, 1980-1981; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Puerto Ricans in New York City, 1959-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Women’s Struggle, 1975-1980; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Economy & Poverty, 1967-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Working Women, 1979-; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Mex-Americans, 1976-; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Chicanos, 1969-1980; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Dairy Farming, 1957-; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Blacks Rebel Miami Florida, 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Health Medicare, 1962-1966; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Welfare, 1961-1977; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Urban Rebellions, 1967-1971; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Welfare (Economy-Domestic Conditions), 1966-1969; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Native Americans Housing/Unemployment, 1958-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Native Americans Resistance, 1969-1979; 2.0 folders (Box 9, Folder 26-27)
- Native Americans Graphics, 1978-; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Native Americans Reactionaries/Support, 1957-1977; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Police Brutality, 1985-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Labor & The Elections, 1938-1978; 4.0 folders (Box 9, Folder 31-34)
- Latino Struggle, 1978-1980; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Black Panthers, 1968-1977; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Black Panthers Party, 1966-1972; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Panther Breakfast Program, 1967-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Black Panther Party – Political Trials, 1968-1970; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Boston – Racist Attack, Apr. 6, 1976-; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Affirmative Action Bakke, 1977-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Civil Rights, 1957-1971; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Civil Rights-Demonstrations, 1954-1969; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Civil Rights Discrimination-Employment Strikes, 1963-; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 44)
- March on Washington, 1963-; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Black Muslims, 1962-1965; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Little Rock, Arkansas, 1957-1958; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Black Organizations, Miscellaneous – organizations and groups, 1967-1971; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Integration – Education – Charlotte, NC, Winston-Salem, Nashville, Tenn, San Antonio, Texas, Virginia, NYC NY, Freeport LI, Florida, Boston, Mass, San Francisco, Calif – School Integration from “TENDER WARRIORS”, 1957-1958; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Civil Rights – Liberties Tallahassee, Florida Rape of 19 Year Old Negro Coed, 1959-; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Chaney-Goodman-Schwerner, 1964-; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Civil Liberties – Discrimination Pilgrimage to Washington, D.C., May 17, 1957; 1.0 folder (Box 9, Folder 52)
- Black Struggle, 1961-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Black Struggle Old Photos, 1953-1962; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Till, Emmitt Louis Till Murder, 1955-1956; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Black Struggle Civil Rights, 1957-1959; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Civil Rights US Civil Rights Commission, 1958-1959; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Black Struggle, 1960-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Civil Rights – Monroe, North Carolina “KISSING CASE” David “Fuzzy” Simpson & Hanover Thompson, Mrs. Jennie Simpson, Mrs. Evelyn Thompson, Dr. A. E. Perry, Robert F. Williams — Mrs. Mary Ruth Reid Assault Case, Rev TH Harris, 1950-1960; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Malcolm X March in Brooklyn, 1986-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Black Struggle Civil Rights – 1963, 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Demonstrations – Anti-Klan, 1986-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Demonstrations – Labor, 1986-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Demonstrations – Labor, 1981-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Demonstrations – Mexico, 1988-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Labor Day, 1988-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Demonstrations Libya, 1986-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Demonstrations – Grenada, 1983-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Demonstrations – Irish Support, 1981-1983; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Palestine Demonstrations, 1988-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 18)
- LA8 – Palestinians, 1987-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Demonstrations – Lebanon & other Mideast, 1975-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Demonstrations – Poland (Domestic – International), 1980-1984; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Demonstrations – Parks, 1989-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Demonstrations – Prison, 1988-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Tompkins Square Park Demo, 1986-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Demonstrations – Pollution, 1986-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Persian Gulf Protests, etc., 1988-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Racism, skinhead, 1989-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Racism Demonstrations, 1986-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Demonstrations – Rate Hikes, 1987-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 29)
- EPA Miscellaneous, 1984-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Demonstrations – Old Age, Social Security, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Rape Demonstrations, 1988-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Sanctuary, 1984-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Demonstrations Seabrook, 1986-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Demo Union Carbide, 1984-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Demonstrations – Veterans, 1982-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Vietnam Vets, 1985-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Wilson/Train wreck & subsequent Demonstrations, 1987-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Gentrification, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Homelessness, 1982-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Famine, 1984-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Freeway Hall Case Seattle Sociologist, 1975-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Family, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Feminist, 1987-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Food, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Food & Central America Conference, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Farms, 1984-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Freeze, Salt, Talks, etc., 1982-1983; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Former Officials, 1980-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Great Peace March, 1986-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Gambling & Lotteries, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Gay & Lesbian, 1982-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Gay & Lesbian Movement, 1984-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Genetics, 1987-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 54)
- Gramm-Rudman, 1986-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Greenpeace, 1983-1993; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 56)
- Grey Panthers, 1981-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 57)
- Guns/Control, 1989-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 58)
- Guardian Angels, 1983-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 59)
- Harlem, 1985-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 60)
- Hard Times, 1971-1982; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 61)
- Health and Hospital, 1989-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 62)
- High Tec, undated; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 63)
- Heritage Conservations, undated; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 64)
- Homeless, 1989-1990; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 65)
- Homeless, 1989-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 66)
- Homeless Rallies, etc., 1983-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 67)
- Housing, 1982-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 68)
- A bat [(?)] New York 12 Shelter, 1985-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 69)
- [Homeless], 1979-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 70)
- Housing/Homeless, 1988-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 71)
- Hunger, 1982-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 72)
- Health, 1982-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 73)
- Housing Demonstrations, 1977-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 74)
- Housing, 1976-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 75)
- HUD, 1989-; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 76)
- Demo Philippines, 1986-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 10, Folder 77)
- Industry, 1982-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Jesse Jackson Campaign, 1980-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 2)
- [Japanese Americans], 1981-; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 3)
- [Immigration], 1979-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Incineration, 1985-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Iran/Contra Scandal, 1986-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Ollie North & Friends, 1987-; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Ollie North, 1985-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Immigration – INS see also Refugees, 1984-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Housing [Oversize], 1986-; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Immigration Refugees Sanctuary, 1979-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Filipinos in U.S., 1986-; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Klan, Nazis, Avowed Racists, 1976-1990; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Labor – Picket Lines, 1974-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Columbia, 1984-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Labor – Phelps Dodge, 1984-; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Labor Picket – Hotel Workers, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Latinos, 1982-1983; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Law & Order, 1981-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Leadership – Left, 1982-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Leaders – Latino, 1976-; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Leaders – Business, 1981-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Leaders – Women, 1980-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Left Groups, 1979-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Legal Aid, 1987-; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Martin Luther King Day Parades, etc., 1988-; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Medicare, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Media People – Celebs, 1982-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Media Scand[al]s, 1987-; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Medicine, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Migrant Workers, 1982-1983; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Nuke Energy, 1979-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Occupational Safety and Health, 1977-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Nuclear Weapons Demonstrations, 1984-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 34)
- [New Bedford], undated; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Nature Miscellaneous and Natural Disasters, 1989-; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 36)
- American Indians, 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Native Americans, 1979-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 38)
- New Right, 1982-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 39)
- National Rifle Association, 1986-; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Native Americans, 1958-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 41)
- “MOVE”, 1985-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Moonies, 1981-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 43)
- Minimum Wage, 1989-; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Mobster, Gambling, Underground, 1983-; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Mining, 1984-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Weapons, 1985-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 47)
- Military Hardware and War Games, 1980-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 48)
- New York City, 1984-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 49)
- Military Mugs Miscellaneous, 1981-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 50)
- Planned Parenthood, 1981-; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 51)
- Racism, 1986-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 52)
- Political Prisoners, 1987-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 53)
- Poverty Programs/Cutbacks, 1976-1983; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 54)
- Political Trials, 1981-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 55)
- Pope/Religion, 1982-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 56)
- Porn, 1984-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 57)
- Politicians, 1980-1984; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 58)
- Prisons, 1982-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 59)
- [Green River Murders], 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 60)
- Public Works, 1983-; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 61)
- Puerto Rican Nationalists, 1979-; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 62)
- Radiation, undated; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 63)
- Rainbow, 1988-1990; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 64)
- Rape, 1982-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 65)
- Upstate Racism, 1988-; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 66)
- Reagan Administration --Attorney General & Justice Meese, Turner, Reynolds, 1982-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 67)
- Reagan Administration -- Ambassadors, 1981-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 68)
- Reagan Administration --Agriculture, 1980-1983; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 69)
- Reagan Administration -- Chief of Staff, 1981-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 70)
- Reagan Administration -- CIA – Casey, 1986-; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 71)
- Reagan Administration -- Defense, 1981-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 72)
- Reagan Administration -- Commerce, 1982-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 73)
- Reagan Administration -- Education, 1985-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 74)
- Reagan Administration -- Energy, 1980-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 75)
- Reagan Administration -- Health & Human Services, 1981-1983; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 76)
- Reagan Administration -- Budget, 1981-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 77)
- Reagan Administration -- EPA, 1981-1983; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 78)
- Reagan Administration -- Federal Reserve, 1980-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 79)
- Reagan Administration -- FTC, 1981-; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 80)
- Reagan Administration -- Interior, 1981-1983; 1.0 folder (Box 11, Folder 81)
- Reagan Administration -- Housing & Urban Development HUD, 1980-1983; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Reagan Administration -- Labor, 1981-1982; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Reagan Administration -- McFarlane, 1984-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Reagan Administration -- Press Secretary, 1981-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Reagan Administration -- Vice President Bush, 1980-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Reagan Administration -- Transportation, 1981-1983; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Reagan Administration -- Secretary of State, 1981-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Reagan Administration -- Treasury, 1981-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Reagan Administration -- Miscellaneous, 1981-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Repression: CIA, FBI, Police, Immigration Justice, 1950-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Refugees outside U.S./ Miscellaneous, 1985-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Republicans, 1981-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Repression, 1982-1984; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Red-Baiting, 1953-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Religion, 1982-1986; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 15)
- [Peace], 1983-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Refugees outside U.S./ Haiti, 1981-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Refugees, Illegal Aliens, Immigrants, 1981-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Demonstrations – Women, 1971-1984; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Women-Equal + Abortion Rights Demonstrations, 1970-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Women ♀-Jobs (usual + unusual) + Personalities, 1969-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Women in Government, undated; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Puerto Rico, 1977-1979; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 23)
- FALN, 1977-1980; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Democratic Convention, 1968-; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Peace Resistance 1968, 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Disarmament, 1962-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Birth Control, 1969-1971; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Housing, 1964-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Gay Struggle, 1977-1979; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Gay Rights, 1979-; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 31)
- U.S. Capitalism Graphics, 1968-1979; 3.0 folders (Box 12, Folder 32-34)
- U.S. Imperialism Graphics, 1970-1979; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Chile – Demonstrations in U.S., 1973-1977; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Salt II, 1979-; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Farm Workers and Chicanos, 1976-1979; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 38)
- U.S. Capitalism-Photos, 1941-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 39)
- U.S. Capitalism, 1976-1979; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Cutbacks – NYC, 1971-1977; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 41)
- People’s and Democratic Conventions NYC, 1980-; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 42)
- 1929 Crash, 1945-1979; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 43)
- [Strikes], 1978-1979; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Strikes, 1979-; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 45)
- U.S. Politics, undated; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Busing, 1974-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 47)
- Senior Citizens, 1935-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 48)
- Cartoons, etc., 1977-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 49)
- Arms Control, 1977-; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 50)
- Day Care, 1973-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 51)
- Inflation, 1966-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 52)
- Asians Struggle/U.S., 1978-; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 53)
- Workers, 1978-; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 54)
- Refugees – Exiles, Concentration Camp Victims, etc., 1953-1969; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 55)
- Busing (Boston, etc.), 1971-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 12, Folder 56)
- Busing, 1971-1977; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Immigration, 1977-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Poverty – U.S. Minorities, 1966-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Jimmy Carter, 1976-1979; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Campaign - 1976, 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Education, 1970-1980; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Teaching Equipment and Methods, 1960-1979; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 7)
- NYC Crisis, 1975-; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 8)
- U.S. Congress, 1974-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 9)
- U.S Bicentennial, 1976-; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 10)
- International Hotel Demonstrations S.F., 1977-; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Peace Corp, 1961-1968; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Chinese, 1970-1979; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Right Wingers, 1961-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Bombings, 1967-1971; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 15)
- “Human Rights”, 1977-; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Commissions [Warren], 1964-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 17)
- UN Meeting and International Politics, 1954-1975; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 18)
- National Black Convention, 1971-1972; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Poverty – U.S. Whites, 1949-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 20)
- U.S. Support Demonstrations – PLO, 1976-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 21)
- U.S. Support Demonstrations – Africa, 1977-; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Misc. Demonstrat[ions], 1960-1971; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 23)
- U.S. Support Demonstrations – Iran, 1978-1979; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 24)
- U.S. Support Demonstrations – Asia, 1977-1979; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 25)
- U.S. Support Demonstrations – Latin America, 1978-1979; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Cutback Demonstrations, 1974-1979; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Sports Olympics, 1952-1968; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Peoples Struggles-Democratic Freedom/Peace/Community Control, 1979-; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Sports, 1978-; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Sports, 1951-1987; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Teachers, 1959-1987; 3.0 folders (Box 13, Folder 32-34)
- Transit Striker – NYC, 1966-; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Transit – Bus, Truck, Taxi, Subway, 1954-1976; 2.0 folders (Box 13, Folder 36-37)
- Teamsters/TDU, 1959-1982; 2.0 folders (Box 13, Folder 38)
- TWU STK, 1980-; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 39)
- Unemployment, 1963-1983; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 40)
- Unemployment, 1981-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 41)
- University Workers, undated; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 42)
- World Federation of Trade Unions (Industry & Labor), 1985-; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 43)
- Corporate Heads & Executives (Industry & Labor), 1961-1969; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 44)
- Facilities Industry – Factories, 1959-1965; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 45)
- George Meany, 1955-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 46)
- “Movie Salt of the Earth Film of the Striking Miners of New Mexico”, 1965-; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 47)
- Workers, 1976-1980; 2.0 folders (Box 13, Folder 48-49)
- China Agriculture, 1958-1976; 1.0 folder (Box 13, Folder 50)
- China, 1941-1974; 4.0 folders (Box 13, Folder 51-54)
- China cont., 1971-1975; 3.0 folders (Box 14, Folder 1-3)
- China, 1933-1976; 3.0 folders (Box 14, Folder 4-6)
- Bombing of Dru, 1960-1974; 1.0 folder (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Cambodia Places, 1973-1978; 1.0 folder (Box 14, Folder 8)
- [Cambodia], 1973-; 1.0 folder (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Laos-Cambodian Conflict (late ‘70s) Chinese-Vietnamese Conflict (late ‘70s) etc., 1978-1979; 1.0 folder (Box 14, Folder 10-11)
- Cambodia, 1973-1979; 1.0 folder (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Cambodia Civilians (Casualties & Other), 1964-1980; 1.0 folder (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Khmer Rouge, 1979-; 1.0 folder (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Vietnamese People After Liberation, 1978-1985; 1.0 folder (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Unemployed, 1984-1988; 1.0 folder (Box 14, Folder 16)
- [Oversized Photos], 1982-1989; 1.0 folder (Box 14, Folder 17)
- [Illustrated published materials most likely used for photograph research], 1965-1989; 7.0 folders (Box 14, Folder 18-21,23)
- North Korea, 1982-; 1.0 folder (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Original Artwork "Our Roots Are Still Alive", 1947-1968; 1.0 folder (Box 15)
- Hugo Gellert Artwork, 1981-; 1.0 folder (Box 15)
- Oversized photos, folders (Box 15)
- Record album covers, book covers, and related graphics, folders (Box 15)
- Oversized cartoons (some originals) and graphics, folders (Box 15)
- Collages and created graphics, folders (Box 15)
- Some original layouts, folders (Box 15)
- Book Art MP, 1983-; 1.0 folder (Box 15)
- Poster Art MP, 1983-; 1.0 folder (Box 15)